You're lying.
I told you.
My son doesn't lie.
Oh my God.
No wonder
she looked familiar.
You truly are
the Knights' owner.
Oh my God.
What have I done?
You have
a lot of nerve.
First you destroy
a three-million-dollar
painting of mine,
and then you
try hitting on me?
Tell me, Allen,
how do you plan
on paying for this?
What? Pay for that?
Three million?
Even if I sold myself,
I could never
pay that off.
Oh no.
No, no...
It's all
a misunderstanding.
I mean, he was
just being impulsive.
Please, please, please,
have mercy on us.
Absolutely.
A misunderstanding,
huh?
Was it
a misunderstanding
when you
insulted us earlier?
Ted.
Allen absolutely
knows he's wrong.
Yes.
We're very,
very sorry.
Can you let
this go, please?
Please.
Obviously,
you have
loads of money.
I mean,
you're not gonna
miss a few million.
But this would
ruin my family.
You want me
to forgive him?
Please.
If I were the one
who damaged
the property,
would you be so
quick to forgive me?
Listen,
you can mock me
all you'd like,
but don't ever
insult my father.